Lionel Kevin D. Natividad

Angeles City, Pampanga, Philippines | 09063519099 | lionel.natividad@gmail.com

PROFILE

a committed and flexible professional with experience in leadership roles who has transitioned into the exciting field of web development. I have a strong foundation in HTML, CSS, and Javascript and have a track record of success in management roles. experienced in building aesthetically pleasing, user-friendly, and useful online applications using the Bootstrap and React frameworks.

RELEVANT LINKS

Github: <u>Lionel Kevin Natividad</u>
Portfolio: <u>Lionel Kevin Natividad</u>

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

KodeGo Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Inknovative Portfolio Website

May 2023-July 2023

- Tools Used: React, Javascript, and CSS
- Provide back-end, API as well as front-end codes during application development.
- Led the team in building the front-end as well as the backend website from scratch

WORK EXPERIENCE

LCN Surplus Center and Enterprises

Manager/Supervisor

Angeles City, Pampanga 2018-Present

- Oversee the overall business operations focusing on maximizing smooth and efficient management and resource allocation.
- Manage a robust client network, diligently addressing clients' needs and requests to fulfill their diverse requirements.
- Site inspection prior to equipment and resource deployment.

JCI ANGELES CITY CULIAT

Angeles City, Pampanga

Director for Branding

2022-2023

- Oversee that all branding guidelines are enforced in social media postings.
- Ensure consistency of the organization's visual elements (logos, colors, etc.).
- Development and execution of comprehensive brand strategies in alignment with the organization's mission, vision, and values.

KEY SKILLS/ TECH STACK

Front-end: HTML, CSS, and Javascript

Collaboration tools: Google Suite, Zoom, and Microsoft

Office

Back-end: Node.js and express.js

Database: mySQL

EDUCATION

HOLY ANGEL UNIVERSITY

Angeles City

Bachelor of Science in Human Resource Development and Management

Batch 2018